LX Jordon Bobo

(801) 386-3402 Millcreek, UT. 84124

jordon.bobo@outlook.com github.com/JordonBobo linkedin.com/in/jordon-bobo/

Summary

2 years of experience developing and maintaining computer scripts. Strong analytic skills that made it possible to adhere to federal compliance standards in systems with protected information. Certification in Full Stack Programming with the University of Utah.

Technical Skills JavaScript ReactJS Node.JS MySQL

MongoDB HTML/CSS Heroku Handlebars

Projects

Middle Earth Supplier

middleearthsupplier.herokuapp.com

Collaboration with 3 other programmers to build an online retail website with fictional products to demonstrate functionality and style. Has an employee section which requires a login to access.

GitHub repo: github.com/JordonBobo/MiddleEarthSupplier

Tools used: Handlebars, MySQL, Sequalize, Express, Node, GSAP, Bootstrap, jQuery

Travel Quiz jordonbobo.github.io/JSQuiz02-Travel/

A small fun quiz app that lets users answer questions to get travel suggestions. Built for mobile or desktop users.

<u>GitHub repo</u>: github.com/JordonBobo/JSQuiz02-Travel <u>Tools used</u>: JavaScript, jQuery, CSS, HTML, Bootstrap

Alpha Investments

jordonbobo.github.io/AlphaInvestments/

An investing website that shows company information, stock performance, and current news headlines for publicly traded US companies. Collaboration project with 4 other programmers.

<u>GitHub repo</u>: github.com/JordonBobo/AlphaInvestments <u>Tools used</u>: Chart.js, Ajax, Alpha Vantage API, NYTimes API

Experience

Utah Higher Education Assistance Authority (UHEAA). Salt Lake City, UT.

Systems Support Specialist

May 2019 - Feb 2021

- Extensive multitasking in order to complete overlapping projects and tasks without overlooking any key system or variable.
- Fostered a collaboration focused environment to develop, maintain, and improve inhouse software.

Processor Jan 2018 – May 2019

• Exceeded all expected accomplishment standards by more than 20% with the lowest number of quality assurance issues in the department.

Murray City Corporation. Murray, UT

Library Services Aide

Nov 2013 – July 2017

- Facilitated the library's acquisition and implementation of new ILS software and Self Service Machines.
- Administered meetings which concluded how to best utilize \$50,000+ annual capital expenditures budget.

Education

University of Utah Coding Bootcamp

Nov 2020 - June 2021

Certificate in Full Stack Web Development

Utah State University.

Graduated May 2013

Bachelor of Arts in History